nstar.com 2007-10-10

# NSTAR: Privacy Statement & Disclaimer

NSTAR respects the privacy of our customers.  We realize that customer concerns about privacy and the secure transfer, storage, and use of personal customer information have increased with the growth of online services and the Internet.  That’s why NSTAR has developed the privacy policies described here and uses state-of-the-art technologies to safeguard customer information.

**What kind of information do we collect?  
**When you visit our web site, there are two kinds of information that we are likely to record:

  * **Non-personal statistical information.**   This is anonymous information on subjects such as:  how many visitors come to our web site, how they navigate through the site, which browsers they use to visit the site, etc.
  * **Personal information that you supply to us.**   When you sign up for certain services, or register on the NSTAR web site to access your account information, or when paying bills electronically, NSTAR will collect personal information that will help us to identify you, authenticate you, process your payments and provide you better service in the future.  This information is called “personally identifiable information,” and is used to associate usage information with a specific individual or entity.  Examples of personally identifiable information are:  customer name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, and account number.  When you apply for service, we will also need you to provide your social security number, and if you pay your bill or purchase a gift certificate through the Internet either by check or by use of a credit card, we will need certain information regarding your bank account and/or credit card account.

It is a common business practice to collect “personally identifiable information” in order to conduct business and provide customers with specific services.  In fact, NSTAR has collected much of this information from customers in the past to provide services through the mail or over the telephone.  The emergence and popularity of the Internet provides NSTAR with yet another way to communicate with customers and meet customer needs, though we recognize and respect the heightened awareness that consumers have with regard to information transmitted over the Internet. 

**Do we sell or trade customer information?  
**No. NSTAR will not sell or trade your personal information to any third party, absent specific authorization by you.  We only collect your personal data in order to provide you with better service.  We do provide account information, including the customer of record’s social security number, to collection agencies.

**Receipts of E-mail  
**E-mail gives NSTAR another convenient way to communicate with our customers.  We hope to tell you from time to time about new rates, products, and services that might be of interest or benefit to you.  NSTAR will not, however, send you e-mails if you do not wish to receive them.  If at anytime you would like to remove yourself from NSTAR’s e-mail list, you can do so by updating your profile information or by typing “Remove” in the subject line of a returned e-mail to us.

**Security  
**All transfers of personal information on our web site, www.nstar.com, are secured by the industry standard Secure Sockets Layers (SSL) protocol.  SSL prohibits other web users from gaining access to your personal information. In addition, we comply with all Federal and state regulations relative to the protection from disclosure of your personal information both on and off-line, and we have developed strict internal policies designed to protect your personally identifiable information from unauthorized access.

**Children  
**NSTAR does not seek to collect personal information from children under 18 years of age.  In addition, you should know that we do not have any content on our site that would be considered harmful to children and that we do not restrict children from visiting our site.

**Linked Web Sites  
**NSTAR's web site contains links to various other web sites that are not owned or operated by us.  Please be aware that these other sites may have privacy policies that differ from NSTAR’s and that we cannot be responsible for their content.

**Updates  
**In order to improve our service or to keep up with future industry changes, the information in this privacy policy may be periodically updated.  We will post a new date in the event that the current policy is altered.  This statement was posted February 2007.

**Disclaimer  
**By accessing this site, you are deemed to agree to the acceptance of the following terms:  all contents of this web site are copyrighted to NSTAR as of February 2007.  The basis on which you are entitled to access the NSTAR site is set out below.  These terms may be changed from time to time.

The NSTAR web site pages contain a selection of material concerning NSTAR.  The material is for information only.  All trademarks, logos, button icons and other identifiers are the registered and unregistered trademarks of NSTAR and its subsidiaries and may not be displayed or used without our express written consent. NSTAR may at any time alter the contents of the pages on the web site, refer the reader to other sites on the World Wide Web, and/or remove pages from the web site. 

Users of this web site agree not to distribute nor reuse the content of this site, engage in any unlawful or abusive conduct in the use of the site, or alter or interfere with the use of the site in any way.

NSTAR does not make any representations or warranties, express or implied, about the information provided through this web site, including any hypertext links or any other items used either directly or indirectly from the web site.  NSTAR does not accept any responsibility for enabling the reader to link to another site in the World Wide Web or for any other site.

NSTAR does not represent that the information contained on the web site is accurate, comprehensive, verified or complete, and except as specifically provided by law shall have no liability for the accuracy of the information contained in the web site or for delays or omissions or for any reliance placed by any person on the information.

Except as specifically required by law, NSTAR shall not be liable for any claims or losses of any nature, arising indirectly or directly from use of the information on the web site.  NSTAR accepts no responsibility for unauthorized access or actions of the reader in respect of these matters.  References herein to NSTAR shall mean NSTAR and all of its direct and indirect subsidiaries.
